

Email Snipe76@gmail.com

Address

Harosh 9a / 18, Beer Sheva, Israel

Phone

+972528733196

Date of birth

Dec 19, 1993

Skills

Programming tools

Debugging and testing skills

A quick and avid learner

Excellent coordination

Languages

English

Advanced

Russian

Native

HebrewNative

Evgeniy Gutman

C Programmer

Dedicated C# Programmer with a strong technical background and over 8 years of experience developing and maintaining software applications. Passionate researcher with a strong knowledge of broad areas, including planning, assessment, design, and features and functionality testing. Highly organized with a good team spirit and an ability to solve complex problems with accuracy and clarity. Looking to join an exciting and innovative organization for a C# developer position.

Experience

Armed Security Guard

Safeguarding and Security Ltd.

2015 - 2019

During my time at the company, I secured many locations such as:

- Soroka hospital (2015-2016)
- IDF army base (2016-2017)
- Government VIP's (2017-2018)
- Project manager (2018-2019)

Game Developer

Bullet Bears

2019 - 2021

My position as a lead programmer required me to:

- Supervise and delegate tasks to a team of [3] people.
- · Pitch ideas on how to improve performance and efficiency
- Consistently meet my short and long-term targets.

Tech Instructor

Beit Yatziv

2021 - 2022

I was teaching kids from the first grade to the seventh grade how to build robots and program them (WeDo2), program microchips (MicroBit), 3D modeling and using 3D printers.

Education

Full matriculation

Yitzhak Rabin Highschool Beer Sheva, Israel

Sep 2006 - Jul 2012

- Provided assistance to struggling students.
- Expanded study subject: Art
- · Honors in English

Game Developer

Tiltan College Haifa, Israel

2017 - 2019

I studied:

- · Game design
- Programming
- · Unity & Unreal 4 engines